Lesson two, Bob returns home with bad news.
Bob tells his wife Susan that he lost his job.
Susan suggests that he starred his own business.
What's the matter, dear?
Susan, I got canned today at work.
But Bob, you were Peter's right-hand man.
Yes, and he stabbed me in the back.
Keep your chin up.
Maybe he'll change his mind and take you back.
When pigs fly, once he makes up his mind, he never changes it.
Besides, I told him off.
Look on the bright side.
You won't have to set eyes on Peter ever again.
Thank goodness for that.
Hang in there.
I'm sure you won't be out of work for long.
In the meantime, we'll have to live from hand to mouth.
Don't get too stressed out, Bob.
We'll make ends meet.
I can always get a job in McDonald's as a last resort.
I don't think they're hiring right now.
If worse comes to worst, we can sell our home
and move into a tent.
Let's think big.
Maybe you can start your own business.
Easier said than done.